Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve death!
Mimosa!
Your new opponent is right here!
Be gone, boy!
He's still got that recovery magic!
I can't finish him off!
What now?
Why are you just sitting there, insect?
Listen to me.
I am royalty, Asta.
And you...
are the first commoner I've accepted.
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up until you beat him.
Understand?
Yeah, I'll bring this guy down, and I'll get one or two hits in for you while I'm at it.
I live to destroy the weak!
Well, you're not gonna destroy me!
I may not have any magic power, but what I do have...
are my friends!
I don't really know how, but...
I did it.
Oh...
uh...
scanning
caswear
Vou...
これは...
ふと、僕ら 目を閉じては
Was I?
gon
Time
Fujita
brand
Myanmar
Happy
Android
God
It's
F
Let's go!
Set on!
I'm dead.
He's...
hit...
ASTA!
I'm fine!
Forget about me for now and go look after him!
Alright, sure.
This wound...
Can I even heal it with the magic power I have left?
ASTA! Open up your eyes, brat!
Where did all that arrogance go?
You can't die before we fight!
ASTA! Try to hold on.
You can do it!
Do you hear me? You're not alone!
Mars, is our training getting to you?
When things get tough, just close your eyes and think about the people you love.
That's why we're here.
We were born so we could become powerful enough to protect our country.
Once we've gotten strong, that's when we'll get to leave this place.
Do you think you'll be the first one who goes?
I do.
I mean...
How could you not be?
You're the strongest.
We all know it.
If I get out...
I'll wait.
I promise.
I'll wait for you.
Yeah.
We'll go see the outside world together.
This is your final test.
A fight to the death.
Only the last one standing will be permitted to leave here as a mage in service to our country.
Refuse, and you will all be eliminated.
You're the worst, and you will die.
You've been eliminated.
No!
Mars, I'm sorry.
Anna?
This is the only way.
Now die.
It seems Mars is the survivor.
Which means he will be the one that gets the magestones.
As for his compound magic, let's use Fauna.
Both for her abilities and because she was the last he defeated.
And thus, from the deaths of his peers, the mightiest mage is born.
I... I don't need anyone.
As powerful as I am, I will never need anyone.
Those who don't have power are weak.
And the weak die.
Impossible.
He can still move?
Give up.
You're a pathetic, helpless little child.
You never stood a chance of defeating me.
No, Asda!
This is our chance.
Asda's last slash dispel his flame recovery magic.
We could finish him off right now.
Almost there.
A little longer and I'll break through this binding.
Now die.
Asda!
No matter which spell I pull from my Grim War, it'll be too late.
I can't let him die.
Not like this!
You never need the prophecy.
Oh, my God's heart.
Yes.
Because you weren't still on fire going.
You don't need to feel like the despair.
I did not feel like this
can be used to last a while too.
You don't care.
It's too late.
You don't know me too, Yoshi.
You don't care whether you Creo War.
I must be here.
What happened here?
I won't leave you for a leon attack.
Uh...
You
What happened is it over did you know finish him the binding spell it's broken
You know, what did you do? Yeah, really? What magic was that? I?
Don't know don't know what there was this tiny person a tiny person I think
You must be tired we can discuss this later. There will be time
He's down now for good
This writing is it from that scroll
Oh
Well, that's just great a trap spell the ceilings caving it's going to collapse
Celestial wind art everybody get on
Time to leave
Now let's go mimosa look after Rasta I will
Yeah, you've got to please don't speak
You've got help him too
What are you saying Osta did you forget that he's been trying to kill us we were sent here
Set to protect the dungeon's treasure
To keep the things you're safe not to kill
He's got a point it would be a shame to let such a tough guy just die like that, you know
There's no time leave him. Let's go
Where's the exit?
Mimosa can't keep healing Osta and guide us out
Make her right now I can guide us out of here. Yeah, sure
Left here
Left here, okay
Okay, full speed ahead got it
I hit it
They're still coming right on it
But you're my friend you're our friend, so let us help
We've got to save him
I won't let you die
We will get him out alive
Keep fighting
There's our exit
light war
In June
Ah
Mimosa
transformed
It's gone
And yet you kind of started
That was also the way
We made it out
It was so close
Oh that was fun huh
Lunatic
Let's head that way
I'm saved very considerate of them to forge a path for me like that
Of course it helped that nobody could see me hermits thick smoke is certainly a useful spell
Right there all the time and not a single one of them noticed
Well anyway good thing you didn't die back there. That would have been a real shame
Mars I'm sorry
Anna this is the only way now die
ah
Why did you whyy ph legislature
What's your wounds I had to do it partners
I'm sorry
Oh, finally waking up over there, Mars?
Lotus?
That was some good work you did, kid.
Just look at all the treasure I was able to salvage thanks to you.
Think of all the delicious food this will buy our people back home.
My daughters will be eating well after a haul like this.
It's coming back. All of it.
Now go see the outside world. You've earned it.
Live your life, Mars.
For both of us.
Lotus?
Hmm?
You saved me. Thank you.
Hmm.
Well, all right.
So it appears you can say thank you.
Hey, gang.
Asta.
Hi.
Welcome back.
Hey, you made it.
Ow, ow, that hurts.
Uh, yes, well, I suppose it's a good thing you didn't die.
It was close for a while there, but you recovered very quickly.
His sturdiness is about all he's got going for him.
Hey, be nice to the injured guy.
I may not be a lady killer like you, but I've got plenty of good quality.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't have enough magic power to heal you completely.
It was more like first aid, so maybe don't move.
It's not that bad, really.
It might be dead if it weren't for you.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, no, it's...
Sure.
You know, I was sure you were going to kick it before we got to fight.
Not a chance.
No dying for me.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Not until I become the Wizard King.
Poor Asta, you wish.
I am going to become the Wizard King.
Did I give you permission to use me as a crutch?
Come on, I'm just leaning here for a sec.
You too.
Klaus, sir?
I'd have something to say.
I'm so very sorry.
I rejected you both because you're commoners.
And for that, I am ashamed.
You two are exemplary magic knights.
The Order is lucky to have you.
Sir.
Sir?
A bit too tight.
That kind of hurts, Sir Spectacles.
That again?
After everything I said.
You're right, I should start calling you Mr. Softyspecs.
You truly don't know when to quit, do you, brat?
Too serious is Klaus's natural state.
Hey, you know.
Let's fight.
You want to?
Spore with me, please.
I'll pass.
Noelle!
Huh?
Looks like I'm not the only one with torn clothes.
Ah!
Whoops!
He's dead.
Are you okay?
Oh no!
What did I do?
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
He's wake up.
Ah!
What are you looking at?
Creep!
Gah!
Hmm.
Hm.
Heh.
Oh no!
乾いた感情が あの日の僕を見つめ 突き動かしてる
I give our place to go
消えそうな光でも 闇を照らす力が
繋がって時の流れを変える
I love you living in me
色褪せない場所に
Pray for yourself
終わらない夢を掴むため 進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive?
このままどこまででも
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive now, we can drive now
たとえ明日から見えなくても
声にならない想いを抱いて
叫び続ける in my heart
クローファークリプス
So you can say it
You saved me
Thank you, Lotus
Well, alright
So it appears you can say thank you
Yes, I can
Then do you think you can say this?
Peter Piper picked a pack of pickled peppers
Sally sells seashells by the seashore
Rubber baby buggy bumpers
Yes, I can
Peter Piper packed of Sally shells
Sells by the seashore
Rubber baby baby
Bobby Abox
I guess you can't say it
Yes, I can
Peter Piper packed a pick a pick
Sally shells she shells
Buy the rubber baby
Bobby a box
Bogba
Fine, I can't
Yes, did you see that?
I did it, Sister Lily
Wait, I did what?
Meet the Wizard King?
Black Clover, page 20,
Assembly of the Royal Capital?
My magic is being super loud and annoying!